

KONG SREYLIS

IT (Information Technology)

Personal Info

Gender Female

DOB 29 September

2002

Nationality Khmer

Marital Single

Contact Me

526 St., Sangkat Teok Laak1 Khan Toul Kork, Phnom Penh

+(855) 15939602

kongsreylis675@gmail.com

Hard Skill

Computer Programming

C, C++,C#, Java.

Development languages

HTML, tailwind, CSS, SCSS, JQuery, Basic Javascript, php and the Basic framework Laravel, database SQL and Network.

Design

Can use Figma and also GitHub.

Soft Skill

- -Learn new things and Leadership.
- -Patient and sociable.
- -Loyalty and Honestly.

Languages

English Good

Khmer Native

References

Ms.Born Sokeav study at National University of Management.

About Me

I am a hardworking and ambitious individual with a great passion for Technology and computer and can learn a new Challenging. I have just completed my year 3 recently and studying Information Technology at National University of Management. I have excellent communication skill, and I am seeing positions in the industry in which I can put into practice my knowledge and experience that I work for.

Work Experience

Phsar Tech Solution Company 2023-2023

Internship at Phsar Tech Solution Company for 3 month for Web Developer.

Jessica International School

2018-2020

Worked as Teacher English at Jessica International School.

Education Background

Bachelor Degree

2020-Present

National University of Management

Bachelor of Information Technology

High School Diploma 2017-2020

Sunny Wu Somrung Thom High School

- Study grade 12 in Kandal Province.
- · Study grade 11 in Kandal Province.
- Certificate of Excellence for Outstanding Student



Trained Course

Jessica International School

• Successfully finished Ms.Word, Excel, Power Point.

ETEC Center I.T

 Successfully finished Web Design and Computer Programming.